fitfuel.com 2008-12-16

# FitFuel.com - Nutritional Supplements, Organic Foods, Fitness Apparel, Sporting, Anti-Aging

Privacy - Frequently Asked Questions

Fit Fuel is committed to protecting your personal information. As a reminder, Fit Fuel does not request personal information via e-mail or telemarketing. If someone contacts you in this manner and requests personal information on behalf of Fit Fuel, _DO NOT RESPOND_! Delete, disregard or hang up. These questions are not from us. We want your personal information to remain private. If you have questions about Fit Fuel's privacy practices, contact [**privacy@fitfuel.com**](mailto:privacy@fitfuel.com) or call us Toll-Free at **1-877-2-FITFUEL**.

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

Fit Fuel, LLC follows these privacy principles both online and offline in the collection, use, sharing and security of customer information. 

  * Provides you NOTICE of our customer information practices.
  * Gives you CHOICES about how your data may be used for marketing purposes.
  * Provides you the opportunity to UPDATE or CORRECT your personal information.
  * Uses information SECURITY safeguards. 
  * Limits the SHARING of your information. 
  * Commits to COMPLYING with applicable privacy requirements.
  * Provides you with means to CONTACT US about privacy-related issues.

We value the relationship we have with our customers and are committed to responsible information-handling practices. We take great care in safeguarding your personal information and in complying with all applicable federal and state privacy laws and our own internal standards and best practices. 

**FIT FUEL, LLC PRIVACY POLICY**

The following Privacy Policy describes the information and privacy practices for Fit Fuel, LLC ("Fit Fuel") in occasions or events where your personal information is collected by, or on behalf of, Fit Fuel. When you provide us your personal information, you consent to the information practices described in this policy. 

This Privacy Policy may not apply to Web sites that are accessible through FitFuel.com. Our Web site contains links to other sites operated by third parties, including but not limited to third-party sites that display Fit Fuel trademarks. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those other sites to learn how they collect, use, share and secure your information. 

To assist you with reading through our Privacy Policy, we have provided it in Question and Answer format. 

**WHAT INFORMATION DOES FIT FUEL COLLECT FROM ME?**

We may collect personal information such as: 

  * Your contact information (name, mailing address, phone number, e-mail address).
  * Your billing/shipping information (credit card number, shipping address). 
  * Your personal preferences (product wish lists, hobbies and likes or dislikes relating to the products we may offer).

**WHEN DOES FIT FUEL COLLECT INFORMATION FROM ME?**

While shopping or taking advantage of services available from us, we may ask that you provide personal information. For example, we request personal information when you: 

  * Set up an account online
  * Purchase products or services 
  * Schedule delivery or installation 
  * Join a loyalty program 
  * Participate in a sweepstakes, promotion or survey 
  * Contact us with a question or concern 
  * Participate in other activities with Fit Fuel

When submitting personal information through an online form, we will identify which fields are required in order to fulfill your request. 

**HOW IS MY INFORMATION USED?**

We use the information you provide in order to: 

  * Fulfill requests for products, services or information
  * Administer loyalty programs 
  * Provide customer services 
  * Administer sweepstakes, promotions or surveys 
  * Offer new products and services 
  * Improve the effectiveness of our Web site, our marketing endeavors and our services and offers 
  * Conduct research and analysis 
  * Send marketing communications 
  * Perform other business activities 

**WHAT INFORMATION IS PROVIDED TO FIT FUEL FROM OTHERS?**

Information From/About Friends or Family 

If you provide us information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason it was provided. Information From Third Parties 

Fit Fuel obtains consumer information from third-party providers in order to improve the accuracy of our customer database, increase our understanding of our customers or to identify potential customers. 

**DOES FIT FUEL SHARE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OTHERS?**

Fit Fuel does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. 

We may need to share your personal information with certain third parties such as our agents, service providers and other representatives acting on our behalf for limited purposes. For example, we may share personal information with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as: 

  * Fulfilling our customers' orders
  * Sending Fit Fuel marketing communications
  * Delivering packages 
  * Scheduling and performing installations 
  * Servicing products
  * Maintaining our loyalty program
  * Fulfilling subscription services 
  * Conducting research, analysis or administering surveys 
  * Sending regular mail and e-mail on behalf of Fit Fuel 
  * Processing credit card payments 

The third parties with whom we conduct business are only authorized to use your information to perform the service for which they were hired. As part of our agreement with them, they are required to follow the privacy guidelines we provide them and to take reasonable measures to ensure your personal information is secure. 

From time to time, we may be required to share personal information in response to a valid court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful. We may share certain personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of others and ourselves. We may also transfer personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event. 

**DO I HAVE CHOICES REGARDING THE USE OF MY INFORMATION FOR MARKETING PURPOSES?**

Fit Fuel is an opt-out organization. Once we receive your information, we may send you marketing communications that contain valuable offers, promotions and other content. You always have the ability to opt-in or opt-out of receiving future marketing communications from Fit Fuel. 

To opt-out of or opt-in to receiving marketing communications from Fit Fuel, please take one of the following actions: 

  1. Follow the directions on a marketing e-mail or direct mail marketing communication from us.
  2. Call 1-877-2-FITFUEL and provide your current contact information.
  3. Send an e-mail with your current contact information to:  [ **privacy@fitfuel.com**](mailto:privacy@fitfuel.com)
  4. Or, send a request with your current contact information to:  
   Fit Fuel, LLC  
   Attn: Privacy Manager  
   71 Spectrum Blvd,  
   Las Vegas, NV 89101  

If you send an e-mail or letter request, please be sure to include your full name, address, phone number and e-mail address and indicate specifically what type of marketing communication(s) (e.g., e-mail, direct mail and/or phone) you wish to receive or stop receiving. This will ensure we identify you correctly in our systems and accurately process your request. 

Fit Fuel will take appropriate steps to implement your request to opt-out of or opt-in to receiving marketing communications. Please note that due to production, mailing and system timelines, in order to remove you from our marketing lists, it may take up to: 

  * 10 business days for e-mails
  * 30 days for phone calls
  * 6 weeks for direct mail 

Until that change takes effect, you may still receive marketing communications from us. 

Also, please note that even though you may have opted out of receiving marketing communications, you may still receive business-related communications such as order confirmations, product recall information, loyalty program membership status or updates or other organization-related communications. 

**HOW DOES FIT FUEL SECURE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Whether you are shopping online or in our stores, we have security measures in place and take reasonable precautions to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized access of your personal information under our control. Fit Fuel cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us by e-mail, and you do so at your own risk. 

**_Safe Shopping Policy on FitFuel.com/store_**

Because the security of your personal information is a high priority, we have taken numerous steps to ensure that it is processed confidentially, accurately and securely. Fit Fuel uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address and credit card number. 

_Choosing a Personal Password on Fit Fuel Web site_

When you create an online account on FitFuel.com, you need to select a personal password. To maximize your level of protection, you should choose at least 6 characters including a combination of both letters and numbers. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password or any account information. You have the ability to purchase on our site without using a password; however, you will have to reenter your personal information each time you use our site in order to make a purchase. 

**DOES FIT FUEL USE COOKIES, OTHER TECHNOLOGIES OR THIRD PARTIES TO COLLECT INFORMATION ABOUT ME?**

**_Cookies_**

A cookie is a small data file that a Web site or e-mail may send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive. Our Web sites and e-mails use cookies to create a more personalized shopping experience for visitors to our site. Cookies simulate a continuous connection and let us "remember" information about your preferences and session, and allow you to move within areas of our Web sites without reintroducing yourself. 

Fit Fuel uses a third party to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information. Although our cookies may contain a unique user ID, they do not collect or store any of your personally identifiable information. 

**_Third-Party Ad Providers_**

Our Web sites use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and to analyze Web site traffic on our behalf. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our ads. These companies may use technologies similar to those outlined above to measure the effectiveness of ads and e-mails. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites so that we can provide advertisements about goods and services. 

No personally identifiable information is collected in this process. We may share anonymous information with this service provider in an aggregate form, for purposes of analysis and improvement of our site. 

**_Third-Party Solution Providers_**

Fit Fuel, LLC has arranged with PowerReviews, Inc. (d/b/a/ Buzzillions) ("PR") ([http://www.buzzillions.com](http://www.buzzillions.com/)) to facilitate customer reviews of products sold by Fit Fuel, LLC. When you submit a product review to PR, you will be subject to PR's terms of use and privacy policies. The reviews you submit may be posted on both PR's site ([http://www.buzzillions.com](http://www.buzzillions.com/)) and our site. 

**HOW CAN I UPDATE MY INFORMATION?**

Fit Fuel wants your information and marketing preferences to be accurate and complete. We provide several different methods for you to update your personal information. To update your information: 

  1. If you have created an account on FitFuel.com, you can update your information after logging into your account
  2. Call: 1-877-2-FITFUEL
  3. Send a request to: [ **privacy@fitfuel.com**](mailto:privacy@fitfuel.com)
  4. Send a request to:  
   Fit Fuel, LLC, Attn: Customer Care  
   71 Spectrum Blvd,  
   Las Vegas, NV 89101  

If you send an e-mail or letter request, please be sure to indicate your current information and the requested changes you would like made. 

**DOES FIT FUEL COLLECT INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN?**

We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information online from children under the age of 13. We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. 

**WHOM MAY I CONTACT IF I HAVE QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS ABOUT THE PRIVACY OR SECURITY OF MY INFORMATION?**

Please contact our Privacy Manager to report any known or suspected privacy or security breaches or to submit privacy or security-related questions or complaints. After receiving your inquiry, we will respond within five business days. You may contact us in the following ways: 

  1. Call: 1-877-2-FITFUEL
  2. Send a communication to: [ **privacy@fitfuel.com**](mailto:privacy@fitfuel.com)  

  3. Send a letter to:  
   Fit Fuel, LLC, Attn: Privacy Manager  
   71 Spectrum Blvd,  
   Las Vegas, NV 89101

**WILL THIS PRIVACY POLICY CHANGE?**

Because Fit Fuel will continue to implement new technologies and improve the services and features we provide, this policy is subject to change. If there are certain changes or additions to this Privacy Policy, we will post these changes here or in other formats for you to review. If we change our information practives or our Privacy Policy in such a way that your personal information may be used or shared in a different manner, we will give you the opportunity to opt-out of having your information used or share in that new manner. 

_Last Revision Date: April 1, 2007_
